（忆往昔）
是万圣节啊 伙计
It's Halloween, man.
对于我们而言 每天都是万圣节
For us, every day is Halloween.
死亡之神是万圣节的来源
Samhain is the damn origin of Halloween.
凯尔特人相信10月31日晚是一年之中
Celts believed that October 31st was the one night of the year.
生与死之间的隔膜最薄弱的一夜
when the veil was thinnest between the living and the dead.
- 我们今年应该过一次 - 过一次什么
- We should have one this year. - Have one what?
圣诞节
A Christmas!
我们去整棵树 买个波士顿烤鸡
We'll get a tree, a little Boston Market.
就像小时候一样
Just like when we were little.
今天是情人节
It's Valentine's day,
你最喜欢的节日 记起来了吗
your favorite holiday, remember?
你老管它叫什么来着
I mean, what do you always call it?
「自由浪子的圣诞节」
"Unattached drifter Christmas"?
你们人类称他们为「丘比特」
Your people called him "Cupid."
他其实是低等天使
He's actually a lower order of angel.
严格来说 他们是小天使
Technically, it's a cherub,
- 第三阶天使 - 要的要的
- third class.- Yes, yes, yes!
这是开战了吗 我们要开打了吗
Is this a fight? Are we in a fight?
这是他们问好的方式
This is their handshake.
那是怎么回事
What was that?
未来 我们是紧密相连的
The future. We're bonded. ‭
你是释放了我的人
You're the one who set me free.
不 那只是个意外
No, that was an accident.
你和我必将在一起
You and I will be together.
不 那不可能
No, that's… ‭that's not gonna happen.
我们将成为一体
We will become one.
你为什么不想那样
Why wouldn't you want that?
（如今）
（情人节）
（俄亥俄州 哈德森）
来 亲爱的 我来吧
Here, honey. Let me.
谢谢 亲爱的
Thanks, babe.
就跟我们认识那天一样帅
As handsome as the day I met you.
斯黛茜不会敲门吗
Doesn't Staci know to knock?
她要吵醒缇根了
She'll wake Teagan!
抱歉
Sorry.
我按下铃才想起来
I remembered after I rang.
梅丽莎呢
So, where's Melissa?
她在做准备
She's getting ready.
我能尝到她的老妈口红味儿
Eww, I can taste her mom lipstick.
你今晚会告诉她吧
You're telling her tonight, right?
今天是情人节
It's Valentine's Day.
那又如何
So?
这样太无情了
So, that's heartless.
我们不能回头再说吗
Can't we talk about this later?
我等够了
I'm tired of waiting.
我说过了 没那么简单
I-I told you it's not that simple.
梅丽和我还像你这么大时就在一起了
Mel and I, we've been together since we were your age.
我们有一个家 有个孩子
We… we have a house, a baby.
我们有共同的生活
We have a whole life together.
丹 你还不懂吗
Dan, don't you get it?
那正是我想要的
That's what I want.
要么你今晚就告诉她 否则
Either tell her tonight, or…
否则怎么样
Or what?
梅丽莎 你真美啊
Melissa, you look so pretty!
我喜欢你的口红
I love your lipstick.
谢谢 准备好了吗
Thanks. You ready?
真爱 好吗
True love, all right?
大家都继续吧
So everyone just, uh, go back to your sloppy tots.
他走了吗 真的走了吗
Is he gone? Like, gone, gone?
真爱可以带我们离开这里
True love can get us out of here?
嗯
Yeah.
听着
H-hey, listen.
- 嗯 我爱过一百万次了 - 听着
- Yeah, I've been in love a million times. - Listen.
真美啊 迈克 真的
Oh, it's beautiful, Mike. It really…
这黑莓红茶简直太好喝了 辛迪
This bramble grey tea is simply divine, Cindy.
我想为不体谅你哀悼的情绪
I would like to apologize for being so insensitive.
而道歉
to your grieving emotional state.
对了 艺术品真棒
Beautiful artwork, by the way.
你说事实如此
You say it is is how it is,
但我觉得瞎子都看得出
but I think a blind man could see.
贝丝只想离开
that Beth is looking for the door.
我根本不在乎 都注意到了
I barely have a reason to care and even I noticed.
拜托 里克 别那么说我爸妈
Come on, Rick! Don't talk about my parents like that!
听着 莫迪 我也不想戳破
Listen, Morty, I hate to break it to you,
但人们所谓的「爱」 只是一种化学反应
but what people call "love" is just a chemical reaction.
促使动物繁殖
that compels animals to breed.
起初很强烈 莫迪 然后就慢慢消散
It hits hard, Morty, then it slow fades,
让你被一段失败的婚姻束缚
Leaving you stranded in a failing marriage.
我走出来了 你父母也会的
I did it. Your parents are gonna do it.
打破循环吧 莫迪
Break the cycle, Morty.
你吓死我了
You scared the hell out of me!
你怎么来了
What are you doing here?
看看你妈妈
Check on your mom.
莫迪 把螺丝刀给我
Morty, hand me that screwdriver, huh?
感觉真棒
That feels good.
我的离子分离器就要做好了 莫迪
I'm almost finished making my ionic defibulizer, Morty.
会很棒的
It's gonna be great.
听着 里克
Hey, listen, Rick. You know…
[邪恶力量 第11季第13集]
（少女死于「心碎」）
早啊
Morning.
那是吻痕吗
Is that a hickey?
怎么了
And?
昨天是情人节
It was Valentine's Day.
我就是个情种 这又没办法
Can't help it if I'm a hopeless romantic.
你说对了一半
You got half of that right.
只是在尽公民义务
Just doing my civic duty.
帮助各种单身女士
Helping all the single ladies.
知道2月14日最棒的一点吗
You know the best thing about February 14th?
你不非得是真命天子
You don't have to be Mr. Right…
只要出现得及时就行
Just Mr. Right Now.
真有档次
That's classy.
你瞧不起我 那你做了什么
Yeah? What'd you do, judgy?
蜷在你被窝里了吗
Curl up in your snuggie?
- 看电视上播的《五十度灰》吗 - 嗯
- Watch "50 shades" on cable? - Yeah.
没有
No.
看这个
Check this out.
斯黛茜·奥特门 19岁的保姆
Staci Altman, 19-year-old babysitter.
俄亥俄州 哈德森人 昨晚被杀
from Hudson, Ohio, was murdered last night.
真糟糕
Well, that blows.
但如果她不叫阿玛拉 跟我们何干
But if her name's not Amara, how is that us?
因为她的心脏被扯了出来
Because her heart was ripped out.
- 在情人节吗 - 是的
- On Valentine's Day? - Yeah.
是讽刺狼人干的吗
Was it, like, an ironic werewolf?
好吧 我们去看看
All right, we'll check it out.
但首先 我需要培根
But, first, I need bacon.
不 首先 你得冲个澡
No, first, you need a shower.
- 我是不是… - 是的
- Is it… - Yeah.
你说对了
You're not wrong.
我们跟警察都说了
It's like we told the cops.
斯黛茜大概6点左右到的
Staci came over around 6:00.
我们去吃饭了 等回到家时就…
We went to dinner, and by the time we got home…
我们在客厅发现了斯黛茜
We, uh… we found Staci in the living room.
她躺在血泊中 缇根在摇篮里大哭大闹
in a pool blood and Teagan, in her crib, hysterical.
简直太可怕了
It was awful.
你能想到会有什么人
Can you think of any reason.
有什么原因想伤害斯黛茜的吗
why somebody would want to hurt Staci?
想不到
No.
斯黛茜很善良 很受欢迎 又漂亮
Staci was super-sweet and popular and pretty.
每个认识她的人都会爱上她
Anyone who met her fell in love with her.
或许是激情犯罪
Well, maybe it was a crime of passion.
斯黛茜有疯狂前男友吗
Uh, did Staci have any crazy ex-boyfriends?
没有 至少我是不知道
No. N-not that I know of.
你呢
Honey?
我怎么可能知道呢
W-why would I have any idea?
丢了什么东西没有
Was anything stolen?
会不会是抢劫升级
Any chance this may have been a robbery gone wrong?
应该不是
I don't think so.
我们没丢东西
I mean, nothing was missing.
除了起居室里的保姆摄像机
except for the nanny cam in the living room.
多谢配合
Thank you for your time.
如果想到什么就打给我们
Give us a call if something comes up.
好 谢谢
Okay, thank you.
只有我觉得那人的反应有点怪吗
Is it just me, or is that guy acting a bit hinky?
嗯 我也觉得呢
Yeah, I was thinking the same thing.
我们分头行动
Let's split up.
你送我去停尸房
You drop me at the morgue,
然后去办公室找丹
and you can hit Dan at the office.
嗯 或许老婆不在场他会更坦白一些
Yeah, and maybe he'll be a little bit more open without wifey around.
是啊
Yeah.
从尸检情况来看
Based on the autopsy,
被害人心脏被扯出时她是清醒的
the vic was conscious when her heart was ripped out.
我可不想看到那个场面
Wouldn't want a front-row seat to that show.
能想到会是什么东西干的吗
Any ideas what could have done this?
一般来说 我会推定是动物袭击
Typically? I'd assume animal attack.
- 可这是在民居里 - 是啊
- In a house? - Exactly.
而且又没有动物爪印
Plus, no claw marks.
跟你老实说吧 探员
I'll be honest with you, agent.
我做验尸20多年了
Been doing this for some 20-odd years,
这回是难住了
and I'm stumped.
好吧
All right.
谢谢了
Thanks.
有人想见你 哈珀先生
Someone's here to see you, Mr. Harper.
联调局的维勒特工
FBI… an Agent Weller?
请他进来吧
Send him in, please.
请坐吧 探员
Please. Have a seat, agent.
有什么可以帮你的
What can I help you with?
我需要你跟我实话实说 丹
I need you be straight with me, Dan.
我不明白你的意思 探员
I'm not sure what you mean, agent.
我觉得你明白的
Oh, I think you do.
我觉得你有所隐瞒
I think you're hiding something.
而且不想当着你妻子的面说
And you didn't want to talk about it in front of your wife.
你跟保姆有一腿
You're schtupping the babysitter.
什么
Excuse me?
别装生气了
Oh, don't act all fake offended.
我是在帮你呢
I'm actually trying to help you out here, okay?
我个人根本不在乎你睡谁
Now, personally, I don't a give rat's ass who you screw.
但我不希望你的「课余活动」
But I would just hate for your, uh, extracurricular activities.
害你卷进一宗联邦凶杀案调查之中
to get you involved in a federal murder investigation.
或者我也可以去找你妻子谈谈
Or I could just go talk to your wife.
我想跟你说实话 探员
I want to be straight with you, agent.
我真的想 但我不能
I really do, but I can't.
怎么不能
Sure you can.
不 真的 这事太怪了
No, really, I mean, this is just too damn weird.
你不会相信我的
You… you'd never believe me.
说说看
Try me.
我猜猜 是失踪的保姆摄像机吗
Let me guess… the missing nanny cam?
我的确跟斯黛茜有私情
I was having an affair with Staci.
我拿走保姆摄像机
I only took the nanny cam.
是因为她在摄像机前吻过我
because she kissed me in front of it.
我忘记那东西摆在那里了
I forgot the damn thing was there.
总之 我本想等一回家就抹去记录的
Anyway, I was gonna erase it as soon as we got home.
结果我们却看到了斯黛茜的尸体
But then we found Staci's body.
梅丽莎上楼去看孩子了 我…
Melissa went upstairs to the baby, and I…
就去拿摄像机了
Ran for the cam?
我知道这很混蛋
I know it was a dick move,
但我也知道摄像机一定拍下了杀人过程
but I also know the cam must have recorded the murder.
我抹去了那一吻后
As soon as I erased the kiss,
本打算把摄像机交给警方的
I was gonna turn it over to the cops.
我发誓
I swear.
直到我看到了上面的内容
Until I saw what was on it.
我知道那是我 但那真不是我
I know that's me, but I swear it wasn't me.
我绝不会伤害斯黛茜的
I would never hurt Staci.
我爱她
I loved her.
我当时一直在餐厅
I was at a dinner the entire time.
如果你不信 可以问梅丽莎和侍应生
If you don't believe me, ask Melissa or the waiter.
还有其他75位客人
Or any of the 75 other people that were there.
你得相信我
You got to believe me.
放松
Relax.
我信你
I do.
你信我
You do?
你别慌
I need you to sit tight.
这事暂时不要说出去 好吗
Keep a lid on this for the time being, okay?
有发现吗
Find anything?
嗯…没有
Uh, yeah… jack.
完全没有表明是狼人的迹象
Absolutely nothing points to a werewolf.
好吧
Well…
靠边站吧 书呆子
Step aside, Urkel.
是丹偷走了保姆摄像机
It was Dan that stole the nanny cam.
为什么
Why?
他跟保姆有一腿
He was schtupping the sitter.
等等
Wait a second.
我以为丹当时跟梅丽莎去吃饭了
I thought Dan was at dinner with Melissa.
那不是丹
That's not Dan.
易形者
A shapeshifter.
是啊
Yahtzee.
我可以走了吗
It is okay if I head out?
嗯
Yeah.
你没事吧 哈珀先生
Are you okay, Mr. Harper?
如果需要 我愿意留下
I'm happy to stay if you need me.
或许你该回家了
Or maybe you should go home.
跟家人待在一起
Be with your family.
我没事的 格莱蒂斯
I'll be okay, Gladys.
你晚上愉快
You have a good night.
好
Okay.
不好意思
Excuse me.
你落东西了吗
Did you forget something?
斯黛茜
Staci?
怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
我要你把心给我
I want you to give me your heart.
你死了
You're dead.
这不可能
This, this is impossible.
我看到你的心被扯出来了
I saw your… your heart ripped out of your chest.
求你
Please.
你干什么
What are you doing?
你想要什么
What do you want?
你是最后见到活着的你老板的人
You were the last person to see your boss alive.
你有注意到什么不寻常的事吗
Did you notice anything unusual?
没什么不寻常的
Nothing unusual, per se.
就是有点粗鲁
Just kind of rude.
有个年轻女孩 褐发 挺丰满
This young girl… brunette, buxom,
至多就19岁
couldn't have been more than 19…
我离开时从电梯里走了出来
barreled out of the elevator as I was leaving.
几乎把我撞倒
Nearly knocked me over.
是她吗
Is this her?
是的 就是她
Yeah, that's the girl.
多谢配合 女士
Thank you for your time, ma'am.
可以确认是个易形者
Well, it confirms we're dealing with a shifter.
而且还耍手段扮成死人
Yeah, who's upping its game by impersonating dead people.
- 我猜是那个妻子 - 嗯
- I'm guessing it's the wife. - Yeah.
我们深表哀悼
I'm so sorry for your loss.
我就是…不敢相信
I just can't… I just can't believe it.
这怎么可能啊
I mean… how is this even possible?
我们就想查清这一点
That's what we're trying to figure out.
孩子呢
Where's the baby?
她在我妈妈那里
She's… she's with my mom.
我也不想这样
I hate to have to ask this,
但我有个不好开口的问题要问你
but I-I need to ask you a difficult question.
好吧
Okay.
你是否知道你丈夫
Were you aware that your husband.
跟你的保姆有私情
was having an affair with your babysitter?
是的
Yes.
我知道
I knew.
我知道你们怎么想的
I know what you're thinking…
嫉妒妻子杀死出轨老公
jealous wife kills her cheating husband.
但绝不是那样的
But that couldn't be further from the truth.
我很爱丹
I loved Dan.
我依然爱他
I still do.
听上去或许很可悲
It may sound pathetic,
但我以为我们还会有机会呢
but I thought we still had a chance.
多谢配合
Well, thank you for your time.
我们不打扰你了 你休息吧
We'll leave you alone, let you get some rest.
我们走之前 能麻烦你写一个
Before we go, would you mind just writing down.
电话号码给我们 万一我们再有问题
a phone number where we can get ahold of you.
也好找你
in case we have any more questions?
好的
Yeah, sure.
如果出现什么奇怪或不寻常的事
And if anything strange or out of the ordinary comes up,
一定打给我们
don't hesitate to call.
我们就住在主街的汽车旅馆
We're staying at the motel on main street.
多谢
Thanks.
好吧 梅丽莎不是易形者
All right, so Melissa's not the shifter.
我们又回到起点了
We are back to square zilch.
我需要喝一杯 调整一下 或许约一炮
I need a beer. Regroup, maybe get lucky.
- 你不是才约过吗 - 那是在堪萨斯
- Didn't you just get lucky? - That was in Kansas.
怎么样 一起来吗
What do you say? You with me?
我们去酒吧泡几个心碎的妹子回来
Let's go scrape a few hearts off the barroom floor?
我就算了
Uh, I think I'll pass.
我去查查传说 你做你自己去吧
I'm gonna hit the lore, but you go be you.
随你便
Suit yourself.
（染色艺术）
是我
Hey, it's me.
我好像搞砸了
I-I-I think I messed up.
我不知道怎么回事 但出了岔子
I-I don't what happened, but something went wrong.
丹死了 联调局还各种问问题
Now Dan is dead and the FBI are asking questions.
尽快给我回电
Just call me back asap.
是谁
Who's there?
探员 是你们吗
Agents, is that you?
亲爱的 让我进去
Honey, let me in.
亲爱的 是我
Baby, it's me.
不 不是的
No, it's not.
亲爱的 让我进去吧
Honey, please let me in.
我爱你
I love you.
别担心 亲爱的 我不会伤害你
Don't worry, honey. I'm not gonna hurt you.
我是你丈夫
I'm your husband.
- 查到什么了吗 - 没有
- Hey, any luck? - No.
你约到了吗
You?
没有
Nah.
什么叫「老爸身体」
Hey, what's a "dad bod"?
你好啊…
Hey, there, uh…
一切都好吗
Everything okay?
不好 丹想杀我
No, Dan tried to kill me.
丹 你死去的丈夫 丹吗
Dan, your dead husband, dan?
你们说如果发生了
You told me to come to you.
奇怪或不寻常的事就来找你们的
if anything strange or out-of-the-ordinary happened?
的确发生了 我觉得是我的错
Well, it did, and I think it's all my fault.
好吧 你坐下吧 过来
Okay, why don't you sit down? Come on.
我发誓
I swear.
我是真心爱丹 或许太爱他了
I really did love Dan, maybe a little too much.
我…
I just…
我希望他也爱我
I wanted him to love me back.
所以我去寻求建议
So I got some advice.
我跟我的美发师袒露了他俩出轨的事
and I confided in my hairdresser about the affair.
等等 女人还真这么干啊
Wait. Women actually do that?
她说有办法把他赢回来
And she told me that there was a way to get him back.
我知道她…涉猎了一些东西
I… I knew she, uh, dabbled in stuff.
等等
Wait a second.
你指的是什么样的东西
What kind of stuff are you talking about here?
她自称是白女巫
She calls herself a… white witch.
我不知道你们是不是信那种东西
Listen, I don't know if you believe in that sort of thing.
我一般是不信的 但我走投无路了
I normally don't, but I was desperate.
我猜猜 她给了你一个咒语
Let me guess. She, uh, gave you a spell.
是的 归情咒
Yes. A return-to-love spell.
我只需要念咒
All I had to do was chant it and…
再一吻封印即可
seal it with a kiss.
但我并没想发生这种事的
But I didn't mean for any of this to happen.
我发誓 我只是想要回我丈夫
I swear I… I just wanted my husband back.
你有没有带来一份咒语的副本
Do you happen to have a copy of the spell on you?
有的
Um, yes, yes.
好吧 首先 这不是咒语
Okay, for starters, not a spell.
而是阿拉姆语诅咒
More like an Aramaic curse.
- 什么 - 这个
- What? - This…
大致翻译过来就是「死亡之吻」
roughly translates to "The Kiss of Death""
我发誓 这她可没说过
I swear she never told me that.
传说上怎么说的
What does the lore say?
我根本查不到传说
As far as I can tell, there is no lore.
我猜这是白女巫自制的咒语
My best guess is this was the white witch's home cooking.
太棒了 那么我们都知道什么
Terrific. All right, so what do we know?
你吻谁谁死
Um, if you kiss someone, then they die.
差不多吧 等等
I guess. Wait a second.
你没吻斯黛茜啊
You didn't kiss Staci.
当然没有
No, of course not.
但丹吻了
No, but Dan did.
那么诅咒还可传染吗
So the curse is transmittable?
就像魔法性病
Like a magic STD.
这可以有
Okay, that works.
让人怀念老式的疱疹了
Kind of makes you nostalgic for good, old-fashioned herpes.
天呐
Oh, God.
我害死了丹和斯黛茜
I killed Dan and Staci.
你没有害死任何人
You didn't kill anyone.
这是那个女巫的错
This is all on that witch.
跟我说说
Riddle me this.
如果斯黛茜是第二个被吻 为什么反而先死
Why did Staci die first if she was kissed second?
不知道 或许
I don't know. Maybe.
如果你能把诅咒传出去自己就安全了
you're safe if you can pass the curse on?
如果那人死了 就又回到你这儿了吗
And then if that person dies, then it comes back to you?
那能说得通
I mean, that would make sense.
这就难怪不管这是什么东西
That would explain why whatever this is.
现在又找回到梅丽莎头上了
is working its way back to Melissa.
抱歉 我糊涂了
I'm sorry. I'm confused.
是啊 这的确让人糊涂
Yeah, 'cause it's freaking confusing.
总之 这就像烫手山芋游戏
Look, the long and short… it's like a game of hot potato.
你得一直把它往外传
You got to keep paying it forward.
否则 你就要没命
If you don't, you die.
梅丽莎 诅咒是由你开始
Melissa, this curse started with you.
我觉得它也要由你结束
And I think it wants to end with you.
别担心 我们不会让你有事的
But don't worry, okay? We're not gonna let that happen.
你做了什么
What the hell did you do?!
快走 我们走
Come on. Let's just go.
刚刚还真是顺利
I'd say that went pretty well.
你觉得呢
What do you think?
等等 你是认真的吗
Wait a second. Are you serious?
你觉得让自己染上一个致命诅咒是个好主意吗
You think it's a-a good idea to give yourself a fatal curse?
拿着
Hold that.
现在她不是目标了 不是吗
Well, target's off her back, ain't it?
我只是想说 你不用这样的 做个小白鼠
I'm just saying you don't have to do this… be the guinea pig.
- 什么 - 做殉道者
- What? - The martyr.
想自己承担一切 做这种事
Try and carry the weight by yourself… do this.
我会没事的
I'm gonna be fine, okay?
只要我没事 她就没事
And as long as I'm good, she's good,
这才是重点
and that's the important thing.
再说 这证明了我们的理论 不是吗
Besides, it proved our theory, didn't it…
「死亡之吻」诅咒的确是可传染的
that this whole "Kiss of death" curse is transmittable?
我虽然不求诺贝尔奖
I'm not asking for the Nobel here,
但至少说声「谢谢」啊
but, uh, you know, thank you.
- 你觉得我们有多长时间 - 我不知道
- How long do you think we have? - I don't know.
这东西有没什么规律可循
It's not like this thing is exactly following a pattern.
我都不知道我该找什么
I don't even know what I'm looking for here.
但我们刚刚逃得快
But we cut out of there pretty quick…
- 刚刚怎么回事 - 这样或许争取到了点时间
- What was that? - …So maybe that bought us some time.
我们本认为那东西是个易形者
Um, we think it was something called a shapeshifter,
但这又不可能 因为我往它身体里
but, uh, it can't be because I pumped the thing.
打了一堆银而它毫不退缩
full of silver and it didn't even flinch.
你们是哪门子联调局探员啊
What kind of FBI agents are you?
假的那种
The fake kind.
我们是猎人
We're hunters.
猎人
Hunters?
你只需要知道我们拯救你这样的人
Look, all you need to know is that we save people like you.
不受那样的东西的伤害
from things like that.
就算它不是个易形者 它还是会易形
Even if it's not a shapeshifter, it's still shifting shapes.
如果我们能查明它是什么 就能想办法杀它
If we can figure out what it is, we can find out how to kill it.
好吧 你对白女巫有什么了解
All right, what do you know about the white witch?
不怎么了解
Um, n-not much.
她叫索尼娅
Her name is Sonja.
她怪怪的 我不知道
She's kind of weird. I don't know.
她也就刚做了我的美发师几个月
She's only been my hairdresser for a couple of months.
- 你知道她住哪吗 - 不知道
- Do you where she lives? - Uh, not a clue.
- 她在哪把咒语给你的 - 她沙龙的地下室
- Where did she give you the spell? - In the basement of her salon.
（染色艺术）
染色艺术
The Art of Dyeing.
不能说她没警告过你
Well, can't say she didn't warn you.
好了 车门锁好
All right, just keep the doors locked.
我们回来前别乱走
and stay put until we get back.
除非索尼娅出现
Unless Sonja shows up,
那就拿这个对付她
and then use this on her.
杀不死她 但能放慢她的速度
It won't kill her, but it'll slow her down.
你们认真的吗 我不能持刀伤人啊
Are you serious? I can't stab anyone!
- 拿着 - 听我说
- Come on. - Listen to me.
索尼娅不是普通人
Sonja's not just anyone.
她是个邪恶女巫 她杀了你丈夫
She is a wicked witch who offed your husband.
还企图杀你 如果她出现了
and tried to kill you, so if she shows up here,
你就揍她 捅她
you punch her, you stab her,
如果有必要 拿房子砸她都好
you drop a freaking house on her if you have to.
杀女巫的子弹
Witch killing bullets.
我们得想个更好的名字
We got to come up with a better name than that.
（闲人止步）
柜子锁了
Locked cabinet.
看啊
Looky there.
好了
All right.
找到了
Got it.
看来我们对付的是个灵怪
All right, it looks like we're dealing with a qareen.
没听说过
Never heard of it.
是一种「有形生灵
It's a "creature, corporeal in form,
完全听你命令行事「
a slave to your commands""
那不是很像灯神吗
Kind of like a genie.
大概吧 这儿呢
I guess. Here we go.
念咒 然后接吻
Uh, someone chants the curse and lays a wet one on you.
那么被害人就会受到诱惑 被灵怪所杀
Then the victim is seduced and killed by the qareen.
但灵怪不会变成芭芭拉·伊登的模样
But instead of taking the form of Barbara Eden,
而是呈现出你最深最黑暗的欲念的样子
they present themselves as your deep, darkest desire.
怪不得保姆是丈夫杀的
So it makes sense why the sitter was killed by the husband.
而丈夫又被保姆所杀
and the husband by the sitter.
而梅丽莎被丹袭击
Yeah, and why Melissa was attacked by Dan.
她是真心爱他
She really loved him.
怎么了
What?
知道受诅咒的好处吗
Well, the silver lining about being cursed?
我终于能跟黛西·杜克（电视剧人物）面对面了
I'll finally get some face time with Daisy Duke…
我最深最黑暗的欲念
…My deepest, darkest desire.
- 真的假的 - 七岁起就爱上她了
- Seriously? - Ever since I was 7.
那么是凯瑟琳·巴赫的老版
So Bach,
不是杰西卡·辛普森的新版喽
not Simpson.
两个倒是都不赖
Guess I wouldn't say no to either.
好吧 怎么杀了它
All right, how do we kill it?
刺穿心脏
By stabbing it in its heart.
它胸口上有个大洞啊
Uh, well, given that it's got a giant hole in its chest,
它有心吗
does it even have a heart?
看来不在他身上
Apparently not in him.
持有灵怪心脏者
The person who possesses the qareen's heart.
能控制它
is the one who commands it.
那么是美发师索尼娅喽
So Sonja the hairdresser.
好吧 我们去找心吧
All right, let's find us a heart.
我去楼上
I'll take upstairs.
- 不管 我要去楼上 - 好吧
- Whatever. I'm going upstairs. - Okay.
你有发现吗
You find anything?
我明白的 迪恩
I understand, Dean.
是吗
Is that right?
你内心的渴望
The longing in your heart…
我也感觉到了
I feel it, too.
真是感人
Well, that's touching…
毕竟你根本没心
considering that you don't have a heart…
灵怪
…qareen.
我猜你并不真是联调局喽
I'm guessing you're not really FBI.
你是什么
You're what?
猎人吗
A hunter?
你是个女巫
And you're a witch.
把死亡诅咒当爱情魔咒卖
hocking death curses as love spells.
总得有人去惩罚那些男人
Someone has to punish these men.
但唯一比出轨男人更糟的
But, you know, the only thing worse than a cheating man.
就是出轨还不受罚的男人
is one who gets away with it.
你是个女权主义者啊
You're practically a feminist.
我是什么不重要
Who I am doesn't matter.
真正的问题是 你是什么样的人
The real question is, who are you?
什么意思
What do you mean, who am I?
你是个谜
You're a mystery.
我能看清你的心
I can see inside your heart.
能感觉到你的爱 只是
Feel the love you feel, except…
它裹着一层羞愧
it's cloaked in shame.
对这具躯体…
When it comes to this…
你无法自持
you can't help yourself.
那何必要抵抗呢
So why fight it?
投降吧
Just give in.
为什么伤害梅丽莎
Why hurt Melissa?
她不过是想拯救自己的婚姻
She only wanted to save her marriage.
她们都是如此
They all do.
上百个心碎的女人来找我
Hundreds of heartbroken women come to me,
但她们从不吸取教训
but they never learn.
一个月 一年 总有一天
I mean, a month, a year, however long later,
她们会再回来…
they all come back…
一样的故事 不一样的男人
same story, different man.
所以你就「改良」了诅咒吗
So you tweak the curse?
如今它不止惩罚偷腥的人
Now it not only punishes the cheaters,
还惩罚那些希望浪子回头的蠢女人
but the foolish women who want them back.
看来我不过是在清除白痴而已
Guess I'm just weeding out the idiots.
而你就是下一个
And you're next.
是啊 知道吗 你说得对
Yeah, you know what? You're right.
真正的阿玛拉的确能牵制我
The real Amara does have a hold on me,
但你什么也不是 只是个拙劣的冒牌货
but you are nothing but a cheap imitation.
索尼娅 住手
Sonja, stop!
求你了 适可而止
Please. Enough is enough.
迪恩
Dean?
在
Yeah.
我成功了
So…I got it.
- 是嘛 - 搞定了
- Yeah? - It's done.
- 你没事吧 - 没事
- You good? - Yeah.
你呢
Are you good?
挺好
Yeah.
你要继续吊我胃口吗 还是怎么着
So, are you gonna keep me in suspense here or what?
你指什么
About what?
出现的是谁 巴赫还是辛普森
Who was it? Bach or Simpson?
都不是
Neither.
是阿玛拉
It was Amara.
你吃惊吗
Does that surprise you?
你不吃惊吗
That doesn't surprise you?
说实话吗
Honestly?
说实话
Honestly.
怎么 你真觉得上帝的妹妹
What, you seriously think the sister of god.
是我最深最黑暗的欲念
is my deepest, darkest desire?
- 她不是吗 - 不
- She isn't? - No.
不可能是她
She can't be.
- 为什么不可能 - 为什么
- Why not? - Why?
- 因为如果真是 那就说明我 - 说明你怎样
- Because if she was, then that means I'm… - Means you're what?
和她沆瀣一气 软弱 邪恶
Complicit? Weak? Evil?
都对 还不止
For starters, yeah.
迪恩
Dean.
你真觉得你在这事上有选择吗
Do you honestly think you ever had a choice in the matter?
她可是上帝的妹妹
She's the sister of God.
很不幸 她出于某种原因选中了你
And for some reason, she picked you, and that sucks,
但如果你觉得我会因此责备或者看扁你
but if you think I'm gonna blame you or judge you…
我绝不会的
I'm not.
你知道我是想杀了她的
You know that I want her ass dead.
当然
Yes, of course.
我也知道你或许为此
And I know you've also probably beaten yourself up.
自责得要命
a million times over it,
但那对我们有什么好处
but where has that gotten us?
情况有多糟
Just how bad is it?
此时此地
Standing here right now?
我无比希望能捅她一刀
Every bone in my body wants to run her through.
让她从哪爬出来的就回哪去
Send her back to that hole she crawled out of.
但当我靠近她
But when I'm near her…
就会发生一些奇怪的事
I don't know… something happens.
我无法形容
I can't explain it.
但要说那是欲望或爱 也不对
But to call it desire or love… it's not that.
我完蛋了 伙计
I'm screwed, man.
我们想要杀死黑暗
We want to kill the Darkness.
我们必须杀死黑暗
We need to kill the Darkness.
但我觉得我做不到
And I don't think I can.
很抱歉这么对你
I'm sorry to do that to you, you know?
但等到了关键时刻
But when it comes down to it…
我明白 迪恩
I got it, Dean.